Chasing Coral is a documentary film directed by Jeff Orlowski.
Coral reefs are the nursery for all life in the oceans, a
remarkable ecosystem that sustains us.
Yet with carbon emissions warming the seas, a phenomenon called “coral bleaching”—a sign of mass coral death—has been accelerating
around the world, and the public has no idea of the scale or implication of the catastrophe silently raging underwater.
Himself, played by Andrew Ackerman.
Himself - Additional Featured Scientist, played by Pim Bongaerts.
Himself - Additional Featured Scientist, played by Neal Cantin.
Himself - Scientific Advisor, played by Phil Dustan.
Herself - Scientific Advisor, played by Ruth Gates.
Himself - Additional Featured Scientist, played by Manuel González-Rivero.
Chasing Coral is a 2017 American documentary film about a team of divers, scientists and
photographers around the world who document the disappearance of coral reefs.
Chasing Coral was produced by Exposure Labs and directed by Jeff Orlowski.
It premiered at the 2017 Sundance Film Festival and was released globally
on Netflix as a Netflix Original Documentary in July 2017.
Jeff Orlowski has previously directed the movie Chasing Ice in
2012, which shares a similar plot to Chasing Coral.
The film explores themes of global warming, scuba diving, time lapse
photography, underwater photography, marine biology.